lleitmotif.net 2013-06-30

# Privacy Policy | lleitmotif

1.1.

lleitmotif.net understands that how your information is used and shared is important to you. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information.

1.2.

By visiting lleitmotif.net, you hereby accept this Privacy Policy and expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner prescribed herein. If you object to this use and disclosure, please do not provide any information to or use lleitmotif.net.

2.1.

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at lleitmotif.net. Here are the types of information we gather.

2.2.

Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or provide us in any other ways. Those include your personal details you enter while making an order as well as product pages you are visiting. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our store, and communicating with you.

2.3.

Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses lleitmotif.net, such as your IP address, your web browser type, operating system, URL clickstreams and similar. We use cookies for a number of purposes, for instance, to help ensure the security and authenticity of users, to provide the mechanisms for online shopping and to enable traffic monitoring.

2.4.

Information from Other Sources: We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. Those include for example, updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily; account information, purchase or redemption information, and page-view information from some merchants with which we operate co-branded businesses or for which we provide technical, fulfillment, advertising, or other services.

3.1.

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide certain features for you, such as, product recommendations etc.

3.2.

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of lleitmotif.net's coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only in the events as described below:

a. Agents:  
We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and E-Mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

b. Business Transfers:  
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. Your information may be passed to and used by the associated companies of lleitmotif.net or its successors in title.

c. Protection of lleitmotif.net and Others:  
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to cooperate with law enforcement inquiries and other third parties, to enforce laws and third party rights, such as intellectual property rights; to enforce or apply the Terms and Conditions of lleitmotif.net; or protect the rights, property, or safety of lleitmotif.net, our users, or others.

d. With Your Consent:  
Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

5.1.

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. However, we do not guarantee "perfect security" which does not exist on the Internet.

5.2.

We cannot ensure that all of your communications with our Web site and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from this Website.

6.1.

As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide certain information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to use all the interactive features of lleitmotif.net.

6.2.

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, you will not be able to use certain important features if you do not use cookies.

Our services are not available to children. If you are under 18, please do not submit any personal information to us and you may use lleitmotif.net only with the supervision of your parent or guardian.

Our Web site may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time so that it accurately reflects the regulatory environment and our own data collection and disclosures practices. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 3 days after they are posted on this Web site. You should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.

| 

|   
---  
your cart is empty  
  
Receive emails about our promotion, new product information and news!
